[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these famous philosophers was of Swiss descent?", "correct_answer": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau", "incorrect_answers": ["Michel Foucault", "Friedrich Schiller", "Jean-Paul Sartre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Polish food specialties, oscypek and bryndza are what  type of food?", "correct_answer": "Cheeses", "incorrect_answers": ["Soups", "Salads", "Cakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1983 movie received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture?", "correct_answer": "The Lonely Lady", "incorrect_answers": ["Jaws 3-D", "Hercules", "Two of a Kind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lions may be skilled predators, but they would also eat carrion. What animal is the lions preferred food?", "correct_answer": "Wildebeest", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhinoceros", "Hippopotamus", "Elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the Cheddar cheese originate?", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden", "Scotland", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person is considered as the Father of Computer, as he invented a counting machine called The Difference Engine.", "correct_answer": "Charles Babbage", "incorrect_answers": ["John Vincent Atanasoff", "Blaise Pascal", "Argani Alunan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Oliver and Barbara Rose at the end of the 1989 movie The War of the Roses?", "correct_answer": "Both of them die.", "incorrect_answers": ["They reconcile and live happily ever after.", "Barbara kills Oliver.", "Oliver kills Barbara."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is incorrect?", "correct_answer": "Gerontology studies grammar and syntax.", "incorrect_answers": ["Boxology studies schematic layouts and diagrams.", "Apiology studies bees.", "Potamology studies rivers."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mel Brooks has received which of the following major entertainment awards?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Grammy", "Emmy", "Tony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official language spoken on the territory of Spain?", "correct_answer": "Spanish", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Spanish and Galician", "Spanish and Basque"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous Frenchmans dying words were France. Armee. Josephine!?", "correct_answer": "Napoleon", "incorrect_answers": ["Louis Philippe", "Richelieu", "Louis XIV"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If youre double-jointed, it means you have two joints where normally there is one.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]